chadmart.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy notice**  
Our customer information is intended to help us conduct our business in a professional manner and will not be disclosed to others

We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit [www.chadmart.com](http://www.chadmart.com/) on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.

If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we may need -- to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes

**Credit card security**  
Protecting the safety of your credit card information is important to us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit card information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is the gold standard in Internet encryption technology, which is a fancy way of saying that it's a highly sophisticated method of scrambling data as it travels from your computer to our website's servers.

**Your credit card information is secure**

To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser.

If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, please feel free to place your order with us at [order@chadmart.com](mailto:order@chadmart.com)
